

"I am passionate about what I do and always give 100%. When I commit to a project or task, I don't just complete it, I go the extra mile and make it better than requested."

CONTACT



(208) 697-6882



sam@samantha-skidmore.com



samantha-skidmore.com



Provo, Utah

SOCIAL



/samantha-skidmore



/in/samanthaskidmore

SKILLS

JavaScript React Redux JSON HTML

Bootstrap MongoDB

ux Express N Mongoose

CSS

MySQL Git

NodeJS

WordPress

JQuery

EDUCATION

V School | 2018

Full Stack JavaScript Web Development

Community Association Institute | 2017 CMCA Certified

Pioneer Pacific College
Legal Office Administration

SAMANTHA SKIDMORE

Web Developer

PROFILE

Web Developer with 10 + years in client relations and management. Able to translate client requirements and specifications into a reliable website. Proactive in learning new tools in order to stay on track with the ever-changing technologies.

DEVELOPMENT WORK

 $MyPantry \quad \text{https://github.com/samantha-skidmore/projects/tree/master/completed/business-time} \\ I avaScript, React, HTML, CSS$

- User can search recipes via Edamam recipe API
- Option to add/update personal recipes
- To Build: option to inventory personal pantry, curate recipes based on available pantry ingredients, update pantry via receipt scanning

Smithsonian Art Gallery API https://github.com/samantha-skidmore/projects/tree/master/smithsonian-react-redux
JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS

• Search and view pieces in the Smithsonian Art Gallery

Memories https://github.com/samantha-skidmore/projects/tree/master/rough-projects/my-memories JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS

• Family website for posting pictures and sharing memories through the familysearch.org API

Project Git Repository: https://github.com/samantha-skidmore/projects

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITIES ASSOCIATION COORDINATOR

Coleman Homes – A Toll Brothers Company | August 2015 – June 2017

- Pioneered tasks/responsibilities for this new position
- Organized and developed systems to manage homeowner's associations in 7 active communities
- Represented HOA Board of Directors for all 7 communities within the Boise, Idaho area

SALES, SERVICE and BILLING DISPUTE AGENT

CITI Bank (Sears Credit Cards) | May 2012 - August 2015

- Resolved billing transactions for 50+ customers per day
- Trained and coached 3-5 new hires each week
- Managed unaccounted time, coaching feedback and quality assurance for a team of 20.

CERTIFIED HEALTH COACH

Take Shape for Life | June 2009 - May 2012

- Assisted 30-60 clients a month in weight-loss and weight-management
- Trained and consulted 3-5 health coaches on their clients